<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Vietnamese astrology</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Vietnamese astrology was created to let you get a hold of your
        destiny by using specific identification items such as your name, gender, date
         and time of birth to foresee parts of your future. Want to know more details about your future
        rather than common horoscope that you can find anywhere? Start reading now to get your prediction!  </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="start_reading">Start your reading now</string>

    <string name="view_result">View result</string>
    <string name="empty_name">Empty name error</string>
    <string name="empty_name_error">You must enter your name for the correct prediction.</string>
    <string name="empty_gender_error">You must choose your gender for the correct prediction</string>
    <string name="empty_date_of_birth">You must choose your date of birth for the correct prediction</string>
    <string name="empty_time_of_birth">You must choose your time of birth for the correct prediction</string>
    <string name="empty_place">You must choose your place of birth for the correct prediction</string>
    <string name="gender">Biological Gender</string>
    <string name="female">Female</string>
    <string name="male">Male</string>
    <string name="place">Place of birth</string>
    <string name="here">Vietnam or Laos or Cambodia</string>
    <string name="there">Different places</string>
    <string name="date_of_birth">Date of birth</string>
    <string name="changeDate">Change</string>
    <string name="enter_detail">Enter your correct details so we can predict your future.</string>
    <string name="name_field">Name field</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <!--hour-->
    <string name="mouse">Mouse (23h - 1h)</string>
    <string name="buffalo">Buffalo (1h - 3h)</string>
    <string name="tiger">Tiger (3h - 5h)</string>
    <string name="cat">Cat (5h - 7h)</string>
    <string name="dragon">Dragon (7h - 9h)</string>
    <string name="snake">Snake (9h - 11h)</string>
    <string name="horse">Horse (11h - 13h)</string>
    <string name="goat">Goat (13h - 15h)</string>
    <string name="monkey">Monkey (15h - 17h)</string>
    <string name="chicken">Chicken (17h - 19h)</string>
    <string name="dog">Dog ( 19h - 21h)</string>
    <string name="pig">Pig ( 21h - 23h)</string>
    <string name="time_hint">Note : If you were born on exactly 19h then you belong to the Dog hour instead of the Chicken.</string>
    <string name="was_born">Were born: </string>
    <string name="life">Mệnh: </string>
    <string name="canhthin">Dragon (Canh Thìn)</string>
    <string name="tanty">Snake (Tân Tỵ)</string>
    <string name="nhamngo">Horse (Nhâm Ngọ)</string>
    <string name="quymui">Goat (Quý Mùi)</string>
    <string name="giapthan">Monkey (Giáp Thân)</string>
    <string name="atdau">Chicken (Ất Dậu)</string>
    <string name="binhtuat">Dog (Bính Tuất)</string>
    <string name="dinhhoi">Pig (Đinh Hợi)</string>
    <string name="mauty">Mouse (Mậu Tý)</string>
    <string name="kysuu">Buffalo (Kỷ Sửu)</string>
    <string name="canhdan">Tiger(Canh Dần)</string>
    <string name="tanmao">Cat (Tân Mão)</string>
    <string name="nhamthin">Dragon (Nhâm thìn)</string>
    <string name="quyty">Snake (Quý Tỵ)</string>
    <string name="giapngo">Horse (Giáp Ngọ)</string>
    <string name="atmui">Goat (Ất Mùi)</string>
    <string name="binhthan">Monkey (Bính Thân)</string>
    <string name="dinhdau">Chicken (Đinh Dậu)</string>
    <string name="mautuat">Dog (Mậu Tuất)</string>
    <string name="kyhoi">Pig (Kỷ Hợi)</string>
    <string name="canhty">Mouse (Canh tý) </string>
    <string name="tansuu">Buffalo (Tân Sửu)</string>
    <string name="nhamdan">Tiger (Nhâm Dần)</string>
    <string name="quymao">Cat (Quý Mão)</string>
    <string name="giapthin">Dragon (Giáp Thìn)</string>
    <string name="atty">Snake (Ất Tỵ)</string>
    <string name="binhngo">Horse (Bính Ngọ)</string>
    <string name="dinhmui">GOat (Đinh Mùi)</string>
    <string name="mauthan">Monkey (Mậu Thân)</string>
    <string name="kydau">Chicken (Kỷ Dậu)</string>
    <string name="canhtuat">Dog (Canh Tuất)</string>
    <string name="tanhoi">Pig (Tân Hợi)</string>
    <string name="nhamty">Mouse (Nhâm Tý)</string>
    <string name="quysuu">Buffalo (Quý Sửu)</string>
    <string name="giapdan">Tiger (Giáp Dần)</string>
    <string name="atmao">Cat (Ất Mão)</string>
    <string name="binhthin">Dragon (Bính Thìn)</string>
    <string name="dinhty">Snake (Đinh Tỵ)</string>
    <string name="maungo">Horse (Mậu Ngọ)</string>
    <string name="kymui">Goat (Kỷ Mùi)</string>
    <string name="canhthan">Monkey (Canh Thân)</string>
    <string name="tandau">Chicken (Tân Dậu)</string>
    <string name="nhamtuat">Dog (Nhâm Tuất)</string>
    <string name="quyhoi">Pig (Quý Hợi)</string>
    <string name="giapty">Mouse (Giáp Tý)</string>
    <string name="atsuu">Buffalo (Ất Sửu)</string>
    <string name="binhdan">Tiger (Bính Dần)</string>
    <string name="dinhmao">Cat (Đinh Mão)</string>
    <string name="mauthin">Dragon (Mậu Thìn)</string>
    <string name="kyty">Snake (Kỷ Tỵ)</string>
    <string name="canhngo">Horse (Canh Ngọ)</string>
    <string name="tanmui">Goat (Tân Mùi)</string>
    <string name="nhamthan">Monkey (Nhâm Thân)</string>
    <string name="quydau">Chicken (Quý Dậu)</string>
    <string name="giaptuat">Dog (Giáp Tuất)</string>
    <string name="athoi">Pig (Ất Hợi)</string>
    <string name="binhty">Mouse (Bính Tý)</string>
    <string name="dinhsuu">Buffalo (Đinh Sửu)</string>
    <string name="maudan">Tiger (Mậu Dần)</string>
    <string name="kymao">Cat (Kỷ Mão)</string>
    <string name="kimmenh">Metal Element</string>
    <string name="mocmenh">Wood Element</string>
    <string name="thuymenh">Water Element</string>
    <string name="hoamenh">Fire Element</string>
    <string name="thomenh">Earth Element</string>
    <string name="name">Your name</string>
    <string name="you_was_born"> You were born</string>
    <string name="in_year_of"> in the year of</string>
    <string name="year_belong_to">Your year of birth belongs to </string>
    <string name="fortune_teller_for"> My prediction for </string>
    <string name="gioty">Time of the mouse</string>
    <string name="giosuu">Time of the buffalo</string>
    <string name="giodan">Time of the tiger</string>
    <string name="giomao">Time of the cat</string>
    <string name="giothin">Time of the dragon</string>
    <string name="gioty5">Time of the snake</string>
    <string name="giongo">Time of the horse</string>
    <string name="giomui">Time of the goat</string>
    <string name="giothan">Time of the monkey</string>
    <string name="giodau">Time of the chicken</string>
    <string name="giotuat">Time of the dog</string>
    <string name="giohoi">Time of the pig</string>
    <string name="duong">Yang</string>
    <string name="am">Yin</string>

    <string name="general1">Men born on the year of the horse or the goat with the life fate situated on the Mouse or Buffalo sign \: There
    are a lot of difficulties in life you must face and there won\'t be much time you will be satisfied by the result.
    However if you can overcome the hard time then you will succeed. </string>
    <string name="general2"> You are smart and hardworking.</string>
    <string name="general3"> You are respected and loved by other people.</string>
    <string name="general4"> You will lead a leisure life.</string>
    <string name="general5"> You are ery smart and sharp. You may face lots of difficulties when young.</string>
    <string name="general6"> However there is the star of Thien dia khong on the same spot so you can live a long life.</string>
    <string name="general7"> You will have a standard life style.</string>
    <string name="general8"> You may not have a very good health. Be sure to pay special attention to your lifestyle.</string>
    <string name="general9"> You face lots of difficulties when young like a pure flower getting smashed by the wind.</string>
    <string name="general10"> You Will get rich but you don\'t have a very good health. </string>
    <string name="general11"> You may not be rich but you will live a long life. </string>
    <string name="general12"> Your \"Menh\" has \"Tuan triet\" star on it. It is a bad sign but there are no big star and \"Tuan triet\" is a small star so you won\'t face any problems. You will get
    what you want and live a long happy life.</string>
    <string name="general13"> Your \"Menh\" sign has \"Dia khong\" star, your \"Than\" sign has \"Dia kiep\" star. This combination shows that you are smart
    and sharp. However you will experience more sadness than happiness in your life. There may be more failure than success so you have
    to stay strong and keep things cool to go through it.</string>

    <string name="general14"> Since there is \"Dai hao\" and \"Tieu hao\" stars \(bad stars\) but there are no big star that shines on them you won\'t have bad luck.
    Even though you may not be very smart and bright at school, you will still have money and become a successful person.</string>
    <string name="general15"> Your \"Menh\" or your \"Than\" sign has \"Thien dong\", \"Thien luong\" or \"Pha quan\" stars shinning on it. Bad combination! Be careful with your health!</string>
    <string name="general16"> Your \"Menh\" sign has \"Dia kiep\" star shinning on it, your \"Than\" sign has \"Dia khong\" star on it. This result shows that you are smart and sharp. However you will experience more sadness than happiness in your life. There may be more failure than success so you have
    to stay strong and keep things cool to go through it.</string>
    <string name="general17"> Your \"Menh\" sign has no big star shinning on it. In this situation you will have lots of hardship and labor during your youth.</string>
    <string name="general18"> Your \"Than\" sign is situated on \"Thien di\" sign. This combination shows that you will build your career far from home and it will become very successful.
        You are an active person who loves to travel and to move to new places so you are not very family-oriented. You loves to meet new people and have a huge network
        connection. Most people in this situation experience life in their youth very early compared to other people around their age. They have more experience and lots of
        opportunities to work far from home.</string>
    <string name="general19"> Since your \"Thien di\" sign has \"Tuan triet\" star on it, you will not pass away in your hometown. </string>
    <string name="general20"> Your \"Than\" sign is situated in your \"The thiep\"\(husband/wife\) category and there is the star of "Thai am" on it so you will need lots of help from your husband/wife. You may also be someone who are scared of your husband/wife. </string>
    <string name="general21"> Your \"Than\" sign is situated in your \"The thiep\"\(husband/wife\) category and there is the star of "Tuan triet" on it. Be careful! You may face some difficulties with your marital life. </string>
    <string name="general22"> Your \"Than\" sign is situated on the same place as your "Tai Bach" category, this means you are a hardworking person who want to save lots of money. Your number one concern in life will be money, you work hard to earn money to feed yourself. You have fast management skill with money. You
    make money very fast but career for you is not an important factor as long as you can earn money you will work on whatever field.</string>
    <string name="general23"> You will earn fame before money.</string>
    <string name="general24"> You get rich by making business.</string>
    <string name="general25"> You should try to avoid career in the maritime field as you may have some accidents with working on water.</string>
    <string name="general26"> Your \"Than\" and \"Quan loc\" signs are together, this means you have a clear goal when you are/were studying on what career you are going to choose. You will be faithful to that career until the end.</string>
    <string name="general27"> \"Than\" and \"Phu the\" signs are together so you have some interesting things happening in your love life. You and your love met/will meet under a very special circumstance, you will feel
    like you have known him/her for long time already, you and your love have a strong bond and mostly it happens that you will work on the same field/area. Also, you may have a left-hand
    job. At first you may just do it for pure pleasure but in the long run it will become a successful career in your life.</string>
    <string name="general28"> Your \"Than\" and \"Menh\" signs are in the same spot, you believe in destiny and you may easily give up when things get hard. Your life doesn\'t have much things going on. If you are born rich
    you will stay rich but you are born poor it will be very difficult to become rich.</string>
    <string name="general29"> "Than" and \"Quan loc\" sign Your "Than" and "Quan Loc" signs are together which give a good combination. However you have the star "Tuan triet", "Hoa ky"
    or "Dia kiep" there also, if you are a man your career success will come slow.</string>
    <string name="general30"> "Than" and \"Quan loc\" signs are together = good result. However you have \"Tuan triet\" and \"Sat tinh\"
    star on there also. If you are a girl you should protect yourself from being cheated by bad guys.</string>
    <string name="general31"> You have \"Tang mon\" and \"Bach ho\" stars combined together, you may feel lonely, you may be slow on getting married or have troubles with your marital life but don\'t get discouraged so easily.
    There are other good things in life besides a steady relationship.</string>
    <string name="general32"> Your \"Tha\n" sign is situated on \"Phuc duc\" sign so you have a strong feeling for family and strong sense of belonging to your nation. You like to have a life
    with a big family and have strong bonds with all your family members close or far. Since you have a strong love for your birth country you will likely live there for the rest of your life.</string>
    <string name="general"> Prediction for your \"Than\" and \"Menh\" sign.</string>
    <string name="cungMenhintroduction"> \"Menh\" sign in astrology represents your thoughts, your direction in life, your character and capability. The "Menh" sign is anything
    that happens in those areas mentioned above from the moment of your birth til 30 years old.</string>
    <string name="cungMenhTuvi1"> Your \"Menh\" sign has good stars and is situated in a good place. Hence, if you are a woman, you have a hot and curvy body. If you
    are a man you are tall. You are smart and you will have lots of good luck. You also live a long life.</string>
    <string name="cungMenhTuvi2"> Your \"Menh\" sign is situated in a not suitable area. You may not be very smart but you will live a long life with enough money to lead a standard life.</string>
    <string name="cungMenhTuvi3"> Your character is straigh forward and lenient.</string>
    <string name="cungMenhTuvi4"> You are someone who dare to do what you say and have lots of ideas and strategies. </string>
    <string name="cungMenhTuvi5"> Your \"Menh\" sign has lots of good star on it. You will have all\: power, money and health. You will live a full happy life.</string>
    <string name="cungMenhTuvi6"> Your \"Menh\" sign has \"Tuan triet\" star on it, bad alert! You may have some troubles with your parents or siblings. When you are young you may face
    lots of difficulties and need to move far from home. You also need to pay special attention to your health since you may fall sick easily.</string>
    <string name="cungMenhTuvi7"> However, Your \"Menh\" sign has the star \"Dia khong\" and \"Dia kiep\", which are bad stars. Hence you will be struggling with lots of problems with your career
    and you will always have to think for solutions.</string>
    <string name="cungMenhTuvi8"> Your \"Menh\" sign is situated in the Cat and the Chicken position, also there is the star of "Tham Lang" next. You tend to
    look at life with subjective eyes. Sometimes you want to get isolated from the city life to go to a quiet place. Meditation may
    be a good thing for you.</string>
    <string name="cungMenhTuvi9"> Your \"Menh\" sign has \"Thien phu\", \"Ta phu\" or \"Huu bat\" stars next to it so you are sure to have a rich life.</string>
    <string name="cungMenhTuvi10"> Your \"Menh\" sign has the star of \"Kinh duong\" on it, so if you follow commerce careers you will succeed and become rich.</string>
    <string name="cungMenhTuvi11"> Your \"Menh\" sign is situated on the Snake or Pig position. It has \"That sat\" and \"Dong cung\" star on it and "Tuan triet" star next to it. Hence you
    may not make lots of money although you may have fame/gain some position with your career field.</string>
    <string name="cungMenhTuvi12"> Your \"Menh\" sign is in the same spot as \"Ta phu\" and \"Huu bat\" stars so your life will be wealthy and your words will be very powerful.</string>
    <string name="cungMenhLiemTrinh1"> Your \"Menh\" sign has \"Liem trinh\" star on it so you will have a tall body, heavy bones, dark elbows and strong face features.</string>
    <string name="cungMenhLiemTrinh2"> Your \"Menh\" sign has the star of \"Liem trinh\" and is situated on a good place. Hence, you are righteous,
    straightforward, courageous, strict and hot tempered. You will get wealth and live a long life.</string>
    <string name="cungMenhLiemTrinh3"> Besides, your \"Menh\" sign also has \"Van xuong\" \"Van khuc\" stars on it so you are someone with capability and flexibility.</string>
    <string name="cungMenhLiemTrinh4"> However, because your \"Menh\" sign also has another bad star like \"Sat tinh\" so you may not get what you want (money or career).
    </string>
    <string name="cungMenhLiemTrinh5"> The \"Liem trin\h" star, which is situated in your \"Menh\" sign, is placed at a bad position. Hence you are someone that may be
    harsh and dangerous sometimes, you have the business mind, very handy, like competition. You will tend to follow a career in the technical, industrial
    or hand-craft field. You may be a little weak and have some health problems and can face some accidents if not careful enough. You should build a career far from home
    to have a long life.</string>
    <string name="cungMenhLiemTrinh6"> However, you are lucky to have \"Hoa ky\" and \"Dong cung\" or \"Menh\" sign situated on the Snake or Pig position. You don\'t need to worry about accidents or health problems
    and you will lead a good life.</string>
    <string name="cungMenhThienDong1"> Your \"Menh\" sign has the star of \"Thien dong\". In result you have a curvy but kind of short body with white skin and square face.</string>
    <string name="cungMenhThienDong2"> Your \"Menh\" sign has the star of \"Thien Dong\" situated on a good place. In result you are smart with a forgiving attitude, gentle, like to care about
    others but you are not determined and perseverate. You will likely change your career field. However you will be sure to live a long life with wealth.</string>
    <string name="cungMenhThienDong3"> Besides, since your \"Menh\" sign is in the position of the Snake or the Pig, with the star of \"Thien Dong\", it shows that you are someone who loves adventures and travel.</string>
    <string name="cungMenhThienDong4"> However, with \"Thien dong\" star on \"Menh\" sign, in the position of the Snake or the Pig for someone born on contradicting year will give a negative result. You
    may not achieve what you want.</string>
    <string name="cungMenhThienDong5"> If your \"Menh\" has the star of \"Thien dong\" situated on a good place, but has other bad stars like \"That sat\", \"Thien hinh\" or \"Dong cung\", then you will still
    have enough money to live a standard life but your health will not be very good. You may be careful as you will likely have health problems related to the eyes or digestive system.</string>
    <string name="cungMenhThienDong6"> Your \"Menh\" sign has \"Thien di\" star in a bad position. Hence you may not be very smart, you act impulsively. You are gentle but you are someone
    who gets bored easily. You prefer to play than to work. You will likely live a long life but you will face lots of struggles. You will live a life far from home. Commerce
    will be a good field for you.</string>
    <string name="cungMenhThienDong7"> You usually like to exaggerate things, you may not be careful enough with your words so you tend to make other people unhappy.</string>
    <string name="cungMenhThienDong8">Your \"Menh\" sign is situated in the Horse position, which is a bad thing for the \"Thien dong\" star but you still have a strong business mind.</string>
    <string name="cungMenhThienDong9"> Your \"Menh\" is situated in the position of the Horse or Dog. It is not good with the star of \"Thien dong\" but with the year of birth you are born in it is a good result. Hence you will be sure to get wealth.</string>
    <string name="cungMenhThienDong10"> Your \"Menh\" sign is in the position of the Tiger or the Monkey, with \"Thien luong\" star on it so you will have a bright future with lots of wealth and health.</string>
    <string name="cungMenhThienDong11"> Your \"Menh\" sign has the \"Thai duong\" and \"Dong cung\" stars, with the combination of "That sat" star so you will be working on the technological field or business selling and trading. It will be very good for you.</string>
    <string name="cungMenhThienDong12"> Your \"Menh\" sign has the stars of \"Thai am\", \"Thien dong\" and \"Dong cung\" so they will shine very bright. If you are a girl, you will be a very pretty and lovely girl. </string>
    <string name="cungMenhThienDong13"> However, because your \"Menh\" sign has bad stars on it like "Tang mon" or \"Thien khoc\" \"Thien rieu\" stars so you will drop lots of tears for your loved ones.</string>
    <string name="cungMenhVuKhuc1"> Your \"Menh\" sign has the star of \"Vu khuc\" so you have a curvy body with average height. You usually live a life far from your family and have problems with your parents, your wife or your kids.</string>
    <string name="cungMenhVuKhuc2"> Your \"Menh\" sign has the star of \"Vu khuc\" in a good position. Hence you are smart, strong-willed, have organization skill,
    a business mind, determined, straightforward, You will live a long life full of wealth.</string>
    <string name="cungMenhVuKhuc3"> Your \"Menh\" sign is situated in the Buffalo or Goat position. Although it is a good place but you will have problems with your career, the income
    will be irregular. You will only be able to get rich after 30 years old.</string>
    <string name="cungMenhVuKhuc4"> Your \"Menh\" sign is situated in the Cat position, good with \"Vu khuc\" star so you will get wealth however you will have health problems related to the head area.</string>
    <string name="cungMenhVuKhuc5">Cung mênh có vị trí Dậu, tốt với sao Vũ Khúc, tuy được hưởng giàu sang nhưng bạn hay mắc bệnh nội thương trong người khó chữa,
    hay mắc tai nạn xe cộ. Nếu bạn sinh ở hướng tây bắc, thì số mệnh cực kỳ tốt, có uy quyền hiển hách, khuất phục được những côn đồ gian ác, được nhiều người kính trọng.

    </string>
    <string name="cungMenhVuKhuc6">Cung mệnh có vị trí không tốt với sao Vũ khúc, nên bạn kém thông minh, có tính tham lận và không được
    lương thiện, suốt đời chẳng mấy khi được xứng ý toại lòng, vì công danh trắc trở, tiền tài khó kiếm, thường hay phải bỏ nhà lập nghiệp ở phương xa, hay đi làm
    thợ, nếu có của cải của tiền nhân để lại, rồi cũng phá tán hết, và dĩ nhiên không sống thọ. </string>
    <string name="cungMenhVuKhuc7">Cung mệnh có vị trí không tốt với sao Vũ khúc, trong trường hợp này bạn có nhiều sao tốt xung quanh, nên bạn chuyên về
    thủ công, kỹ thuật hay kinh doanh buôn bán, nhưng khá giả và được hưởng tuổi thọ lâu dài. </string>
    <string name="cungMenhVuKhuc8">Cung mệnh có sao Vũ Khúc đồng cung với sao xấu Phá Quân, nên bạn tất bỏ nhà kiếm ăn phương xa, suốt đời cực khổ vất vả. </string>
    <string name="cungMenhVuKhuc9">Cung mệnh có sao Vũ khúc, sao Phá quân gặp sao Văn Xương, Văn Khúc đồng cung, bạn là người thông minh khéo tay, nên chuyên về kỹ nghệ máy móc. </string>
    <string name="cungMenhThaiDuong1">Cung mệnh bạn có sao Thái Dương, vị trí tốt, nên bạn có thân hình đẫy đà, cao vừa tầm,
    da hồng hào, mặt vuông vắn đầy đặn, có vẻ uy nghi, mặt sáng, dáng điệu đường hoàng, bệ vệ rất thông minh, tính thẳng thắn, cương nghị, hơi
    nóng nảy, nhưng nhân hậu từ thiện được hưởng giàu sang và sống lâu. </string>
    <string name="cungMenhThaiDuong2">Tuy nhiên , cung mệnh lại bị sao xấu là tuần triệt án ngữ, giống như 1 tảng đá đè ánh nắng chói chang của mặt trời,
    thành ra suốt đời không được xứng ý toại lòng, thiếu sức khoẻ, thường có bệnh đau đầu, khí huyết, mắt kém, nếu không xa quê hương lập nghiệp thì khó có thể sống lâu. </string>
    <string name="cungMenhThaiDuong3">Tuy nhiên, cung Mệnh bị sao xấu là tuần triệt án ngữ, tuy mắt kém, thường thiếu sức khoẻ, hay có bệnh đau đầu, nhưng bạn vẫn có tài lộc. </string>
    <string name="cungMenhThaiDuong4">Cung mệnh có vị trí không tốt với sao Thái Dương, nên thân hình bạn nhỏ nhắn, hơi gầy, cao vừa tầm, da xanh xám mặt choắc mắt buồn tẻ,
    má hóp, mắt lộ, cũng khá thông minh, tính cũng nhân hậu từ thiện nhưng hơi ương bướng, lại không kiên trì, mắt kém, hay có bệnh đau đầu, bệnh thần kinh, khí huyết,
    nếu không xa quê hương thì tất không sống lâu được. Về già mới được ăn nhàn sung sướng. </string>
    <string name="cungMenhThaiDuong5">Cung mệnh của bạn ở vị trí Tý hay Hợi, nên bạn là người có đức độ, ham chuộng văn chương, triết học đạo lý. </string>
    <string name="cungMenhThaiDuong6">Cung mệnh của bạn ở vị trí Thân hay Tuất hay Tý, nên dù không tốt cho sao Thái Dương, vẫn không đến nỗi xấu xa lắm, bạn
    vẫn được cơm no áo ấm, chẳng nên lo ngại nhiều về bệnh tật. </string>
    <string name="cungMenhThaiDuong7">Tuy cung mệnh của bạn ở vị trí không tốt vvới sao Thái Dương, nhưng bạn có nhiều sao đẹp bên cạnh, nên bạn tất có công danh,
    tiền tài và được tăng thêm phúc thọ. </string>
    <string name="cungMenhThaiDuong8">Tuy cung mệnh của bạn ở vị trí không tốt với sao Thái Dương, nhưng bạn có sao Tuần Triệt vốn là sao xấu thì nay làm
    cung mệnh tốt đẹp, tuy bạn phải xa quê hương, nhưng được hưởng giàu sang khoẻ mạnh và sống lâu. </string>
    <string name="cungMenhThaiDuong9">Cung mệnh có vị trí không tốt với sao Thái Dương, lại thêm các ngôi sao không tốt như sao Kình Dương, sao Đà la nên
    bạn rất cô đơn, phải lang thang phiêu bạt, thiếu sức khoẻ, hay có bệnh đau đầu, bệnh thần kinh khí huyết, mắt kém. </string>
    <string name="cungMenhThaiDuong10">Cung mệnh của bạn có cả sao Thái âm, mặt trăng mặt trời cùng đồng vị trí nên kém tốt đẹp hơn trường hợp đứng riêng rẻ, do
    2 sao đã làm giảm ánh sáng của nhau. Tuy nhiên vẫn là 1 cung mệnh tốt về sự nghiệp, tiền bạc và sức khoẻ. </string>
    <string name="cungMenhThaiDuong11">Cung mệnh của bạn có cả sao Thái âm,gặp sao Văn Xương hay Văn Khúc hội hợp với các sao Thiên Quí, hay Quốc ấn nên bạn
    là người có văn tài lỗi lạc, hay nguỵ biện, biết trì thủ, biết ứng xử đúng lúc và chắc chắn là được hưởng giàu sang. </string>
    <string name="cungMenhThaiDuong12">Cung mệnh của bạn có cả sao Thái Âm, nhưng do gặp sao Tuần Triệt án ngữ, bình thường tuy không tốt nhưng với trường hợp của bạn,
    lại cực tốt. Bạn là người có sự nghiệp học hành rất cao, có quyền cao chức trọng. </string>
    <string name="cungMenhThaiDuong13">Cung mệnh của bạn có sao Thái Âm, tuy không tốt bạn có cả sao Hoá khoa hoá lộc là những sao tốt, nên chắc chắn bạn là
    người giữ chức lớn trong chính quyền. </string>
    <string name="cungMenhThaiDuong14">Cung mệnh của bạn có sao Thái Âm ở cung hội chiếu, giống như cuộc đời có cả mặt trăng mặt trời thay nhau chiếu sáng, suốt đời
    chắc chắn bạn được hưởng giàu sang, lại gìn giữ được quyền thế và tài lộc bền vững. </string>
    <string name="cungMenhThaiDuong15">Cung mệnh của bạn có sao Cự môn ở vị trí hội chiếu, nên chắc chắn suốt đời được hưởng lộc dồi dào và công danh bền vững. </string>
</resources>



